risecredit.com 2017-07-15

# Privacy Policy | RISE Credit

#### _RISE_ \- PRIVACY POLICY

|   | 

#### EFFECTIVE MARCH 2014  
  
---|---|---  
  
**FACTS**

| 

**WHAT DOES _RISE_ DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
  
**Why?**

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
  
**What?**

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.  This information can include:

  * Social Security number and income
  * Account balances and payment history
  * Credit history and credit scores

**How?**

| 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons _RISE_ chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
**Reasons we can share your personal information**

| 

**Does _RISE_ share?**

| 

**Can you limit this sharing?**  
  
**For our everyday business purposes –** such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, prevent or mitigate fraud, engage in corporate transactions, or report to credit bureaus

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our marketing purposes –** to offer our products and services to you

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –** information about your transactions and experiences

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –** information about your creditworthiness

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you**

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**To limit our sharing**

| 

  * Call (866) 580-1226 to speak to an account representative;
  * Log in to your account at www.risecredit.com and click on “Account Settings”; or
  * Contact us via email: [support@risecredit.com](mailto:support@risecredit.com).

If you are a _new customer_ , we can begin sharing your information thirty (30) days from the date we sent this notice. When you are _no longer a customer_ , we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.  
  
**Questions?**

| 

Call (866) 580-1226 or go to www.risecredit.com  
  
|  |   
  
**What we do**  
  
**How does _RISE_ protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards ( _i.e._ , computer virus protection software, firewalls, 128-bit Secure Socket Layer). Only authorized employees have access.  
  
**How does _RISE_ collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you 

  * Apply for credit
  * Give us your income information
  * Provide employment information
  * Provide account information
  * Give us your contact information

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

  * Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes information about your creditworthiness;
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you; and
  * Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.  
  
**Definitions**  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Financial and nonfinancial companies related by common ownership or control.

  * _Our affiliates include companies that have common corporate ownership with _RISE_ , such as Elevate Credit, Inc., Elevate Credit Service, LLC, Elevate Decision Sciences, LLC, RISE Credit, LLC, and RISE SPV, LLC._

**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Financial and nonfinancial companies not related by common ownership or control.

  * _Nonaffiliates we share with can include direct marketing companies for application resell, direct mail and other purposes._

**Joint Marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

  * _Our joint marketing partners include financial institutions, credit card companies, partners that promote our products, pre-paid debit card providers and other lending companies._

**Other Important Information**  
  
As part of our credit underwriting and information collection process, we will consider bank account information provided by you and we may detect additional bank accounts under your ownership. We also may collect and consider information about you from non-credit reporting agency data providers, including, for example, information about your location and the location of your mobile devices, and publicly available information about you.

**Updating your information:** If you need to update the personal information you have given us, log in to your account at www.risecredit.com and click on the “Account Settings” link or call (866) 580-1226 to speak to an account representative.

**"Do not track":** When someone visits the _RISE_ website, a cookie is placed on the visitor’s computer (if the visitor accepts cookies). The cookie we place on your computer does not contain any of your personally identifiable information. _RISE_ advertises its products and services on websites that you may visit, and _RISE_ uses service providers to place such advertisements. Those service providers (such as Google, Microsoft or Yahoo) may use cookies placed on your computer to show you advertisements for _RISE_ services on other websites. You can opt-out from service providers’ and/or marketers’ use of cookies in this manner by visiting each service provider’s advertising opt-out page or by utilizing “do not track” functionality in your web browser. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the _RISE_ website, you will not be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the _RISE_ website.

**Changes to this privacy policy:** If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we will notify you via email and post the updated privacy policy on the _RISE_ website. Please take note of the “Effective Date” at the top of this privacy policy.

* * *

**Vermont residents:** We will not disclose information about you with affiliates or non-affiliated, third-party companies or financial institutions, other than as required or permitted by law, without your express permission.

**California residents:** We will not share information we collect about you with affiliated or non-affiliated third-parties, except in the limited circumstances permitted under state law, or if you give us your permission.

**North Dakota residents:** We will not disclose information about you with non-affiliated, third-party companies or financial institutions, other than as required or permitted by law, without your express permission.

**Nevada residents:** If you would like more information regarding this notice or Nevada’s law regarding corporate do-not-call registries, you can contact us at the toll-free number or address included in this notice or the Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General at 555 E. Washington Street, Suite 3900, Las Vegas, Nevada 89101; Phone: (702) 486-3132/Email: BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us.  
  
  |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |    
  
**_RISE_ – TEXAS CSO PRIVACY POLICY**

| 

**Effective March 2014**  
  
---|---  
  
**FACTS**

| 

**WHAT DOES RISE  CREDIT SERVICE OF TEXAS, LLC D/B/A _RISE_ (" _RISE_ ") DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
  
**Why?**

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information.  Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing.  Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.   
  
**What?**

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.  This information can include:

•     Social Security number and income

•     Account balances and payment history

•     Credit history and credit scores   
  
**How?**

| 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons _RISE_ chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.   
  
**Reasons we can share your personal information**

| 

**Does _RISE_ share?**

| 

**Can you limit this sharing?**  
  
**For our everyday business purposes** – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, prevent or mitigate fraud, engage in corporate transactions, or report to credit bureaus

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our marketing purposes** – to offer our products and services to you

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your transactions and experiences

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your creditworthiness

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you**

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**To limit our sharing**

| 

•          Call (866) 580-1226 to speak to an account representative;

•          Log in to your account at www.risecredit.com and click on “Account Settings”; or

•          Contact us via email: [support@risecredit.com](mailto:support@risecredit.com).

If you are a _new customer_ , we can begin sharing your information thirty (30) days from the date we sent this notice.  When you are _no longer a customer_ , we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.   
  
**Questions?**

| 

Call (866) 580-1226 or go to www.risecredit.com   
  
|  |   
  
**What we do** ** **  
  
**How does _RISE_ protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards ( _i.e_., computer virus protection software, firewalls, 128-bit Secure Socket Layer).  Only authorized employees have access.   
  
**How does _RISE_ collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

•          Apply for credit

•          Give us your income information

•          Provide employment information

•          Provide account information

•          Give us your contact information

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.   
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

•          Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes information about your creditworthiness;

•          Affiliates from using your information to market to you; and

•          Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  See below for more on your rights under state law.   
  
**Definitions** ** **  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Financial and nonfinancial companies related by common ownership or control.

•          _Our affiliates include companies that have common corporate ownership with RISE, such as Elevate Credit, Inc., Elevate Credit Service, LLC, Elevate Decision Sciences, LLC,  _ _RISE Credit, LLC, and RISE SPV, LLC._    
  
**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Financial and nonfinancial companies not related by common ownership or control.

•          _Nonaffiliates we share with can include direct marketing companies for application resell, direct mail and other purposes._    
  
**Joint Marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

•          _Our joint marketing partners include financial institutions, credit card companies, partners that promote our products, pre-paid debit card providers and other lending companies._    
  
**Other Important Information**  
  
As part of our credit underwriting and information collection process, we will consider bank account information provided by you and we may detect additional bank accounts under your ownership.  We also may collect and consider information about you from non-credit reporting agency data providers, including, for example, information about your location and the location of your mobile devices, and publicly available information about you.

**Updating your information:**   If you need to update the personal information you have given us, log in to your account at www.risecredit.com and click on the “Account Settings” link or call (866) 580-1226 to speak to an account representative.

**“Do not track”:**  When someone visits the _RISE_ website, a cookie is placed on the visitor’s computer (if the visitor accepts cookies).  The cookie we place on your computer does not contain any of your personally identifiable information.  _RISE_ advertises its products and services on websites that you may visit, and _RISE_ uses service providers to place such advertisements.  Those service providers (such as Google, Microsoft or Yahoo) may use cookies placed on your computer to show you advertisements for _RISE_ services on other websites.  You can opt-out from service providers’ and/or marketers’ use of cookies in this manner by visiting each service provider’s advertising opt-out page or by utilizing “do not track” functionality in your web browser.  If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the _RISE_ website, you will not be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the _RISE_ website.

**Changes to this privacy policy:**  If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we will notify you via email and post the updated privacy policy on the _RISE_ website.  Please take note of the “Effective Date” at the top of this privacy policy.  
  
  |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |    
  
**_RISE_ – FIRST FINANCIAL LOAN COMPANY PRIVACY POLICY TEXAS**

| 

**Effective August 2015**  
  
---|---  
  
**FACTS**

| 

**WHAT DOES FIRST FINANCIAL LOAN COMPANY, LLC  DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
  
**Why?**

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information.  Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing.  Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.   
  
**What?**

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.  This information can include:

•     Social Security number and income

•     Account balances and payment history

•     Credit history and credit scores 

If you are a _new customer_ , we can begin sharing your information thirty (30) days from the date we sent this notice. When you are _no longer our customer_ , we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
  
**How?**

| 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons First Financial Loan Company, LLC chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.   
  
**Reasons we can share your personal information**

| 

**Does **First Financial Loan Company, LLC  **share?**

| 

**Can you limit this sharing?**  
  
**For our everyday business purposes** – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, prevent or mitigate fraud, engage in corporate transactions, or report to credit bureaus

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our marketing purposes** – to offer our products and services to you

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your transactions and experiences

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your creditworthiness

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you**

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**Questions?**

| 

Write to: 84 Villa Rd., Greenville, SC 29615  
  
|  |   
  
**What we do** ** **  
  
**How does First Financial Loan Company, LLC protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards ( _i.e_., computer virus protection software, firewalls, 128-bit Secure Socket Layer).  Only authorized employees have access.   
  
**How does First Financial Loan Company, LLC collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

•          Apply for credit

•          Give us your income information

•          Provide employment information

•          Provide account information

•          Give us your contact information

We also collect your personal information from other companies.   
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

•          Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes information about your creditworthiness;

•          Affiliates from using your information to market to you; and

•          Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.    
  
**Definitions** ** **  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Financial and nonfinancial companies related by common ownership or control.

•           _Our affiliates include, but are not limited to, Sentral Financial, LLC and Integrity Texas Funding, LP_  
  
**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Financial and nonfinancial companies not related by common ownership or control.

•       _First Financial Loan Company, LLC  _ _does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you._  
  
**Joint Marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

•          _Our joint marketing partners include financial institutions, credit card companies, partners that promote our products, pre-paid debit card providers and other lending companies._    
  
**Other Important Information**  
  
As part of our credit underwriting and information collection process, we may consider bank account information provided by you and we may detect additional bank accounts under your ownership. We also may collect and consider information about you from non-credit reporting agency data providers and publicly available information about you.  
  
  |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |    
  
**_RISE_ – NCP FINANCE LP PRIVACY POLICY TEXAS**

|  | 

**Effective May 2016**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**FACTS**

| 

**WHAT DOES NCP FINANCE LIMITED PARTNERSHIP ("NCP FINANCE") DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
  
**Why?**

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
  
**What?**

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

• Social Security number and account balances

• Income and assets

• Employment information and credit history and payment history

When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
  
**How?**

| 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons NCP Finance chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
**Reasons we can share your personal information**

| 

**Does NCP Finance  share?**

| 

**Can you limit this sharing?**  
  
**For our everyday business purposes** – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our marketing purposes** – to offer our products and services to you

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your transactions and experiences

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your creditworthiness

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you**

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**Questions?**

| 

Call 937-228-5600  
  
|  |   
  
**Who we are**  
  
 Who is providing this notice?

| NCP Finance Limited Partnership, an Ohio limited partnership  
  
**What we do** ** **  
  
**How does NCP Finance  protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
  
**How does  NCP Finance  collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

• Apply for credit or open an account with us

• Give us your income information or provide employment information

• Provide account information

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates or other companies.  
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

• Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes information about your creditworthiness;

• Affiliates from using your information to market to you; and

• Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  
  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?**

| 

Your choices will apply to everyone on your account - unless you tell us otherwise.  
  
**Definitions** ** **  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and non-financial companies.

• Our affiliates include companies that have a common ownership with NCP Finance, such as NCP Finance Limited Partnership and Schear Financial Services, LLC.   
  
**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and non-financial companies.

• NCP Finance does not share with non-affiliated parties so that they can market products and services to you.  
  
**Joint Marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

• NCP Finance may engage in joint marketing with various credit services organizations.   
  
**Other Important Information**  
  
N/A  
  
  |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |    
  
**_RISE_ – OHIO CSO PRIVACY POLICY**

| 

**Effective March 2014**  
  
---|---  
  
**FACTS**

| 

**WHAT DOES RISE  CREDIT SERVICE OF OHIO, LLC D/B/A _RISE_ (" _RISE_ ") DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
  
**Why?**

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information.  Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing.  Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.   
  
**What?**

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.  This information can include:

•     Social Security number and income

•     Account balances and payment history

•     Credit history and credit scores   
  
**How?**

| 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons _RISE_ chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.   
  
**Reasons we can share your personal information**

| 

**Does _RISE_ share?**

| 

**Can you limit this sharing?**  
  
**For our everyday business purposes** – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, prevent or mitigate fraud, engage in corporate transactions, or report to credit bureaus

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our marketing purposes** – to offer our products and services to you

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your transactions and experiences

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your creditworthiness

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you**

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

Yes

| 

Yes  
  
**To limit our sharing**

| 

•          Call (866) 580-1226 to speak to an account representative;

•          Log in to your account at www.risecredit.com and click on “Account Settings”; or

•          Contact us via email: [support@risecredit.com](mailto:support@risecredit.com).

If you are a _new customer_ , we can begin sharing your information thirty (30) days from the date we sent this notice.  When you are _no longer a customer_ , we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.   
  
**Questions?**

| 

Call (866) 580-1226 or go to www.risecredit.com   
  
|  |   
  
**What we do** ** **  
  
**How does _RISE_ protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards ( _i.e_., computer virus protection software, firewalls, 128-bit Secure Socket Layer).  Only authorized employees have access.   
  
**How does _RISE_ collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

•          Apply for credit

•          Give us your income information

•          Provide employment information

•          Provide account information

•          Give us your contact information

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.   
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

•          Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes information about your creditworthiness;

•          Affiliates from using your information to market to you; and

•          Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  See below for more on your rights under state law.   
  
**Definitions** ** **  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Financial and nonfinancial companies related by common ownership or control.

•          _Our affiliates include companies that have common corporate ownership with RISE, such as Elevate Credit, Inc., Elevate Credit Service, LLC, Elevate Decision Sciences, LLC,  _ _RISE Credit, LLC, and RISE SPV, LLC._    
  
**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Financial and nonfinancial companies not related by common ownership or control.

•          _Nonaffiliates we share with can include direct marketing companies for application resell, direct mail and other purposes._    
  
**Joint Marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

•          _Our joint marketing partners include financial institutions, credit card companies, partners that promote our products, pre-paid debit card providers and other lending companies._    
  
**Other Important Information**  
  
As part of our credit underwriting and information collection process, we will consider bank account information provided by you and we may detect additional bank accounts under your ownership.  We also may collect and consider information about you from non-credit reporting agency data providers, including, for example, information about your location and the location of your mobile devices, and publicly available information about you.

**Updating your information:**   If you need to update the personal information you have given us, log in to your account at www.risecredit.com and click on the “Account Settings” link or call (866) 580-1226 to speak to an account representative.

**“Do not track”:**  When someone visits the _RISE_ website, a cookie is placed on the visitor’s computer (if the visitor accepts cookies).  The cookie we place on your computer does not contain any of your personally identifiable information.  _RISE_ advertises its products and services on websites that you may visit, and _RISE_ uses service providers to place such advertisements.  Those service providers (such as Google, Microsoft or Yahoo) may use cookies placed on your computer to show you advertisements for _RISE_ services on other websites.  You can opt-out from service providers’ and/or marketers’ use of cookies in this manner by visiting each service provider’s advertising opt-out page or by utilizing “do not track” functionality in your web browser.  If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the _RISE_ website, you will not be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the _RISE_ website.

**Changes to this privacy policy:**  If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we will notify you via email and post the updated privacy policy on the _RISE_ website.  Please take note of the “Effective Date” at the top of this privacy policy.  
  
  |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |    
  
**_RISE_ – OHIO SENTRAL FINANCIAL, LLC PRIVACY POLICY**

| 

**Effective August 2015**  
  
---|---  
  
**FACTS**

| 

**WHAT DOES SENTRAL FINANCIAL, LLC  DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
  
**Why?**

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information.  Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing.  Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.   
  
**What?**

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.  This information can include:

•     Social Security number and income

•     Account balances and payment history

•     Credit history and credit scores 

If you are a _new customer_ , we can begin sharing your information thirty (30) days from the date we sent this notice. When you are _no longer our customer_ , we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
  
**How?**

| 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Sentral Financial, LLC chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.   
  
**Reasons we can share your personal information**

| 

**Does   **Sentral Financial, LLC  **share?**

| 

**Can you limit this sharing?**  
  
**For our everyday business purposes** – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, prevent or mitigate fraud, engage in corporate transactions, or report to credit bureaus

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our marketing purposes** – to offer our products and services to you

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your transactions and experiences

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your creditworthiness

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you**

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**Questions?**

| 

Write to:  84 Villa Rd., Greenville, SC 29615  
  
|  |   
  
**What we do** ** **  
  
**How does Sentral Financial, LLC protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards ( _i.e_., computer virus protection software, firewalls, 128-bit Secure Socket Layer).  Only authorized employees have access.   
  
**How does Sentral Financial, LLC collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

•          Apply for credit

•          Give us your income information

•          Provide employment information

•          Provide account information

•          Give us your contact information

We also collect your personal information from other companies.   
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

•          Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes information about your creditworthiness;

•          Affiliates from using your information to market to you; and

•          Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.    
  
**Definitions** ** **  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Financial and nonfinancial companies related by common ownership or control.

•           _Our affiliates include, but are not limited to, First Financial Loan Company, LLC and Integrity Texas Funding, LP_  
  
**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Financial and nonfinancial companies not related by common ownership or control.

•           _Sentral Financial, LLC  _ _does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you._  
  
**Joint Marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

•           _Our joint marketing partners include financial institutions, credit card companies, partners that promote our products, pre-paid card providers and other lending companies._    
  
**Other Important Information**  
  
As part of our credit underwriting and information collection process, we may consider bank account information provided by you and we may detect additional bank accounts under your ownership. We also may collect and consider information about you from non-credit reporting agency data providers and publicly available information about you.  
  
  |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |    
  
**_RISE_ – NCP FINANCE OHIO, LLC PRIVACY POLICY**

|  | 

**Effective April 2015**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**FACTS**

| 

**WHAT DOES NCP FINANCE OHIO, LLC ("NCP FINANCE") DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
  
**Why?**

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
  
**What?**

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

• Social Security number and account balances

• Income and assets

• Employment information and credit history and payment history

When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
  
**How?**

| 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons NCP Finance chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
**Reasons we can share your personal information**

| 

**Does NCP Finance  share?**

| 

**Can you limit this sharing?**  
  
**For our everyday business purposes** – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our marketing purposes** – to offer our products and services to you

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

Yes

| 

No  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your transactions and experiences

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your creditworthiness

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you**

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

No

| 

We don't share  
  
**Questions?**

| 

Call 855-380-4021  
  
|  |   
  
**Who we are**  
  
 Who is providing this notice?

| NCP Finance Ohio, LLC, an Ohio limited liability company  
  
**What we do** ** **  
  
**How does NCP Finance  protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
  
**How does  NCP Finance  collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

• Apply for credit or open an account with us

• Give us your income information or provide employment information

• Provide account information

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates or other companies.  
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

• Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes information about your creditworthiness;

• Affiliates from using your information to market to you; and

• Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you.

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  
  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?**

| 

Your choices will apply to everyone on your account - unless you tell us otherwise.  
  
**Definitions** ** **  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and non-financial companies.

• Our affiliates include companies that have a common ownership with NCP Finance, such as NCP Finance Limited Partnership and Schear Financial Services, LLC.   
  
**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and non-financial companies.

• NCP Finance does not share with non-affiliated parties so that they can market products and services to you.  
  
**Joint Marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

• NCP Finance may engage in joint marketing with various credit services organizations.   
  
**Other Important Information**  
  
N/A  
  
  |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |
